Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sarahdwarren (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
AutoCAD Architecture
Physics
Interior Architecture

Sarah Warren

Digital Content Creator

Washington, District of Columbia, United States

Summary

Combining years in many forms of creative production, direction and analyzing. Providing specializations with Associates Degree in Physics, 3 years education in Architectural Engineering, over 4 years of social media involvement, marketing, and aesthetic design, and creating visual and physical solutions based around art design and brand consistency. With all brings detailed understanding in mathematical mindset and viewpoint to evolving projects for organization and analytical strategies. Architectural designing and experience in softwares including AutoCAD, Revit, and Inventor. Social media marketing and optimizing aesthetic pleasure.

Being a full time self promoted multi media artist provides a lifestyle of innovation and resilience. Having such detailed experience from multiple angles provides myself as a dynamic asset to input many forms of creative direction to a creative team.

Experience

Instagram

Social Media Marketing Specialist January 2015 - Present (8 years 4 months)

Instagram is a social media platform taken as a form of self promotion and advertisement. With this platform I am able to market myself through the use of self made content and engaging with other users with similar interests to make possible collaboration opportunities and more exposure to my yearned for creative community.

- = Worked with multiple brands through social media
- = Page aesthetic designer for major influencer accounts
- = Brand representative for posting content as advertisement

MI VIDA

Team Lead Coordinator
January 2018 - Present (5 years 4 months)

Washington D.C. Metro Area

Long term experienced waitress of over 8 years in the Food and Hospitality industry. I am proficient in making guests feel comfortable and am adaptable to any kind of people. Having worked in multiple states and cities allows me to be easily versatile and relate to anyone I take care of while maintaining optimal guest flow in dining room environments. I strictly maintain a high tolerance for countless given situations as well as professional relationships with my peers and work settings.

- = Walked new server through training process
- = Occasional managing server to assure all other servers properly completed individual tasks given to open or close a restaurant
- = Capable of any position needed to be filled in restaurant to maintain functioning work flow for fellow co workers and guests.

Society6

Art Designer

January 2017 - Present (6 years 4 months)

Society6 provides a platform in which artists, designers, etc., are able to sell their work on multiple print forms. I am able to take any or my 2D artwork and sell in multiple print forms on multiple different appliances. With this plat form people are able to enjoy my artwork in any form of their choosing.

Self-employed

Full-Time Student/Self-Promoted Artist January 2006 - Present (17 years 4 months)

- = Self taught/taught by father how to work with pencil
- = Self taught painter in Acrylic, oil, oil pastels mediums
- = Competed in Multiple art shows through child to current
- = Drawing/painting self made designs for online retail
- = Clay and Pottery work

Florida A&M University

Woodworker

September 2016 - September 2018 (2 years 1 month)

Tallahassee, Florida Area

- = Architectural Engineering projects required for woodwork specializing
- = Specializing in wood machinery and cutting various materials.
- = Following sketch schematics/blueprints to cut and develop wood work
- = Learn to shave and polish multiple textures

=

North Carolina Central University

1 year 5 months

Fab Lab Co Founder

September 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 5 months)

Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina Area

- = Incorporated in STEM scholarship programming Physics
- = Part of group to develop first FABLAB at NCCU
- = Certified with usage of 3D Printers, laser cutters, etc.
- = Opportunity to recreationally create and develop objects that would become convenient for the lab

Electrical Apprentice

September 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 5 months)

Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina Area

- = Learned process and introduction to Electrical engineering.
- = Dissecting schematics and understanding process to electrical developments.
- = Learning how to use energy to electrically transmit energy.
- = Created functioning device for potential company investment.
- = Understanding basic circuit theory and the connection of elements such as resistors, capacitors, diodes, transistors and inductors in a circuit.

Education

Strayer University

Associate's degree, Cyber Security (2019 - 2021)

Florida Agricultural and Mechanical University

Some education, Architecture (2016 - 2018)

North Carolina Central University

Associate's degree, Physics · (2014 - 2016)

Strayer University

Bachelor of Applied Science - BASc, Information Technology · (2019 - 2022)

Strayer University

Bachel, Information Technology · (2019 - 2022)